

FARRUKH SHOAIB

Address: Coast guard saddar karachi

Phone: +92 3462260435

Email: Farrukhmalik411@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a versatile digital marketer with extensive experience in video editing, graphic design, SEO, and social media management. I have worked with various media outlets like Aziznews and Tehkeek TV Channel, as well as numerous international clients. Currently, I manage digital marketing and social media strategies for TheTravels.pk and Hoorain Travel, driving brand growth and customer engagement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aziz News & Tehkeek Tv

2022-2023

- · Work as a social media manager & digital marketer
- Also as a video editor & graphic designer
- · Also doing work as a content creator and seo specialist
- Also work for facebook page of aziznews organic reach and paid also
- I have aslo work for my own business

Thetravel.pk 2023-2024

- · Coordinated testing and validation, ensuring compliance with industry standards.
- Provided technical expertise, contributing to a 15% reduction in system failures.
- And also work as a social media manager, tour guide, and content creator

Hoorain travels 2023-2024

- Managed full lifecycle of a cutting-edge automation project, meeting all milestones.
- Conducted feasibility studies and risk assessments, mitigating potential project risks.
- Collaborated with clients, leading to a 25% increase in customer satisfaction.

EDUCATION

Intermediate 2022-2024

Guards public college saddar karachi

· Commerce student

Course 2023-2024

Aptech garden centre

- · Digital marketing
- · seo & social media marketing.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Social Media Managing, Seo, Video Editing, Graphic Deisgning, Voice Over Artist, Content creator, Thumbnail Designer.
- · Languages: English, German, punjabi.
- · Certifications: Ms Excel, Digital marketing